Did you know if you go to a Philly's
game, the dollar hot dogs
fully loaded,
that's the only way you got them.
You
fully load a dog, you got to split in
half so you can put all the toppings in.
So then you get a sandwich.
But if you
put another hot dog underneath, then all
the toppings that fall out of the first
fully loaded dog
come on to the second
fully loaded dog. You know what I mean?
I do not understand.
Do you eat meat? Are you vegetarian?
Like I don't know what what you did you
eat. Are you hungry?
You know, I like
that pa, but like what's with the hummus?
Like, do you like take it off
like the tree or something?
- Like shave
it and then like cream it up?
- Please.
- Like, how do you do that?
- Can you share your recipe?
- Please get your friend.
I don't like walnuts. Does it have
walnuts in it?
I don't know. I think that's pesto.
Oh god, I don't like these tips. Do you
like these tips?
I don't know which
color looks better on me. What do you
think?
Please
You're my uncle Bone's out there. I
don't know what he's doing though.
He
just said, you know, for me to come in
here and keep you company.
He's like,
"Yeah, like come down to Porttomino.
Like you can go to the beach and then
like you can hang out with my friends."
So, like I don't know. It looks like a
pretty cool place. I think it turns into
a club later.
That'll be fun, right?
What kind of music you like?